<?xml version="1.0"?>
<posts category="short"><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593696064</statusID><post>Apna app hai ree</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593934896</statusID><post>In Loh's paper, he admits he would "be very surprised if this approach has entirely eluded human discovery until the present day, given the 4,000 years of history on this topic", but says the alternative technique &#x2013; which combines steps pioneered by Babylonian, Greek, and French mathematicians &#x2013; is "certainly not widely taught or known (the author could find no evidence of it in English sources)".&#xD;
However, since first sharing his pre-print paper describing the simple proof online in October, Loh says his attention has been drawn to a 1989 research article that is the most similar previous work he has found &#x2013; going some way to justify his disbelief that this alternative method had not been identified before now.&#xD;
"The other work overlapped in almost all calculations, with an apparent logical difference in assuming that every quadratic can be factored, and a pedagogical difference in choice of sign," Loh explained to ScienceAlert in an email.&#xD;
All that remains to be solved then, is the mystery of why this technique hasn't become more widely known previous to this, since it gives us, in Loh's words, "a delightful alternative approach for solving quadratic equations, which is practical for integration into all mainstream curricula".&#xD;
(Not to mention, of course, that it might just mean that nobody need ever again memorise the quadratic formula.)&#xD;
We still don't know how this escaped wider notice for millennia, but if Loh's instincts are right, maths textbooks could be on the verge of a historic rewriting - and we don't take textbook-changing discoveries lightly.&#xD;
"I wanted to share it as widely as possible with the world," Loh says, "because it can demystify a complicated part of maths that makes many people feel that maybe maths is not for them."&#xD;
The research paper is available at pre-print website arXiv.org, and you can read Po-Shen Loh's generalised explanation of the simple proof here.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593934933</statusID><post>In Loh's paper, he admits he would be very surprised if this approach has entirely eluded human discovery until the present day, given the 4,000 years of history on this topic", but says the alternative technique &#x2013; which combines steps pioneered by Babylonian, Greek, and French mathematicians &#x2013; is "certainly not widely taught or known (the author could find no evidence of it in English sources)".&#xD;
However, since first sharing his pre-print paper describing the simple proof online in October, Loh says his attention has been drawn to a 1989 research article that is the most similar previous work he has found &#x2013; going some way to justify his disbelief that this alternative method had not been identified before now.&#xD;
"The other work overlapped in almost all calculations, with an apparent logical difference in assuming that every quadratic can be factored, and a pedagogical difference in choice of sign," Loh explained to ScienceAlert in an email.&#xD;
All that remains to be solved then, is the mystery of why this technique hasn't become more widely known previous to this, since it gives us, in Loh's words, "a delightful alternative approach for solving quadratic equations, which is practical for integration into all mainstream curricula".&#xD;
(Not to mention, of course, that it might just mean that nobody need ever again memorise the quadratic formula.)&#xD;
We still don't know how this escaped wider notice for millennia, but if Loh's instincts are right, maths textbooks could be on the verge of a historic rewriting - and we don't take textbook-changing discoveries lightly.&#xD;
"I wanted to share it as widely as possible with the world," Loh says, "because it can demystify a complicated part of maths that makes many people feel that maybe maths is not for them."&#xD;
The research paper is available at pre-print website arXiv.org, and you can read Po-Shen Loh's generalised explanation of the simple proof here.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593934985</statusID><post>Just a few weeks ago, a report came out claiming that Samsung has dropped all plans of releasing the Galaxy M41 and M51 is supposed to take its place. However, this info seems to be in discrepancy to the 3C certification that the phone cleared on June 28.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
According to the 3C listing, the phone has is very much alive and kicking and more importantly, reveals a juicy detail about the battery. And by juicy, we mean juicy - 6,800 mAh unit is supposed to power up the device. A battery with such charge is comparable to the batteries in some big tablets. There's also a photo of it on the Safety Korea website.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593958058</statusID><post>Hxjsjssj jsjsjss </post><post>Shshhsbshaa shsjjaJust a few weeks ago, a report came out claiming that Samsung has dropped all plans of releasing the Galaxy M41 and M51 is supposed to take its place. However, this info seems to be in discrepancy to the 3C certification that the phone cleared on June 28.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
According to the 3C listing, the phone has is very much alive and kicking and more importantly, reveals a juicy detail about the battery. And by juicy, we mean juicy - 6,800 mAh unit is supposed to power up the device. A battery with such charge is comparable to the batteries in some big tablets. There's also a photo of it on the Safety Korea website.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593958088</statusID><post/><post>Hsjsjsaj shajja</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593958120</statusID><post/><post>Hsjsjs sjsjs sjsjsjaj</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593958174</statusID><topic>Tr</topic><post>Dnsjsjs shsjs</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593958543</statusID><topic>Weekly poll: how often do you change phones?</topic><post>In a poll we conducted a little over two years ago most people stated that they upgrade their phone every two years. Well, did you? Especially now that 5G connectivity, periscope cameras, high refresh rate screens and blazing fast charging have become commonplace.&#xD;
&#xD;
The adoption of these new cutting edge technologies has a downside &#xE2;&#x20AC;&#x201C; premium phones rarely go under $1,000. That said, the quality of mid-range phones has gone up significantly with many now offering near-flagship specs.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593959273</statusID><topic>Samsung Galaxy A51 5G review</topic><post>The A51 5G's back comes with a reimagined finish too. What were seemingly arbitrary intersecting diagonal lines splitting the rear into 4 distinctly textured areas, have now been aligned parallel to the X and Y axes. A vertical border divides the back 4-to-1, the right having a solid color, the left vertically striped.&#xD;
&#xD;
Then, somewhere below the midpoint, the angle of reflection of light changes, and under the right conditions, you can see once again four ever so slightly different portions on the A51 5G's back. It's all a lot more subtle than we can ever manage to put into words. Our review unit is in the Prism Cube White colorway, but the Prism Cubes also come in Pink and Black, with the same underlying design.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593960287</statusID><topic>Vulnerability is an essential element for defining disaster impacts and its threat to people. How and in what ways can vulnerability to disasters be characterized? Discuss different types of vulnerability with reference to disasters.</topic><post>According to United Nation Office of Disaster Risk Reduction (UNDRR), Vulnerability can be defined as the conditions determined by physical, social, economic and environmental factors or processes, which increase the susceptibility of an individual, a community, assets or systems to the impacts of hazards.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vulnerability assessment needs to be based on a systematization and conceptualization of vulnerability describing the main linkages between the different components of risk. Only if the population and decision makers know where and how vulnerable the system is and which social&#x2013;economic, physical, and environmental factors play a major role in it, adequate measures can be implemented to reduce vulnerabilities to disasters. It involves two approaches:&#xD;
&#xD;
Scientific Approach: It includes the research line of practical measurement approaches of vulnerability and disaster risk reduction.&#xD;
Policy Approach: It provides information about the spatial distributions of vulnerability to different natural hazards upon which the authorities need to take actions.&#xD;
Different Types of Vulnerability&#xD;
Physical Vulnerability: The potential for physical impact on the physical environment &#x2013; which can be expressed as elements-at-risk (EaR). The degree of loss to a given EaR or set of EaR resulting from the occurrence of a natural phenomenon of a given magnitude and expressed on a scale from 0 (no damage) to 1 (total damage)&#x201D;.&#xD;
For Example: A wooden house is sometimes less likely to collapse in an earthquake, but it may be more vulnerable in the event of a fire or a hurricane.&#xD;
Economic Vulnerability: The potential impacts of hazards on economic assets and processes (i.e. business interruption, secondary effects such as increased poverty and job loss) vulnerability of different economic sectors.&#xD;
For Example: Families with low incomes often live in high-risk areas around cities, because they can&#x2019;t afford to live in safer (and more expensive) places.&#xD;
Social Vulnerability: The potential impacts of events on groups such as the poor, single parent households, pregnant or lactating women, the handicapped, children, and elderly; consider public awareness of risk, ability of groups to self-cope with catastrophes, and status of institutional structures designed to help them cope.&#xD;
For Example: Women and children are more vulnerable to disasters as compared to men.&#xD;
Environmental Vulnerability: The potential impacts of events on the environment (flora, fauna, ecosystems, biodiversity).&#xD;
For Example: People living in the tropical areas are more vulnerable to tropical cyclones as compared to people living in temperate region.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593962748</statusID><topic>&#x918;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x92C;&#x928;&#x947; &#x938;&#x942;&#x924;&#x940; &#x915;&#x92A;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92B;&#x947;&#x938;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x91C;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x926;&#x93E; &#x938;&#x941;&#x930;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x937;&#x93F;&#x924;, &#x935;&#x948;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91E;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x928;&#x947; &#x90F;&#x915; &#x92A;&#x930;&#x924; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x92C;&#x947;&#x905;&#x938;&#x930; &#x92C;&#x924;&#x93E;&#x92F;&#x93E;</topic><post>&#x905;&#x917;&#x930; &#x906;&#x92A; &#x92E;&#x941;&#x902;&#x939; &#x92A;&#x930; &#x930;&#x942;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x932;, &#x938;&#x94D;&#x91F;&#x949;&#x932; &#x92F;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x94B;&#x908; &#x90F;&#x915; &#x92A;&#x930;&#x924; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x947; &#x92B;&#x947;&#x938;&#x915;&#x935;&#x930; &#x915;&#x93E; &#x907;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x947;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x932; &#x915;&#x930;&#x924;&#x947; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902; &#x924;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x924;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x939;&#x94B; &#x91C;&#x93E;&#x90F;&#x902;&#x964; &#x910;&#x938;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x915;&#x94B;&#x930;&#x94B;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x940; &#x938;&#x902;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x915;&#x923;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x938;&#x947; &#x938;&#x941;&#x930;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x937;&#x93E; &#x928;&#x939;&#x940;&#x902; &#x926;&#x947;&#x924;&#x947;, &#x92C;&#x932;&#x94D;&#x915;&#x93F; &#x916;&#x924;&#x930;&#x93E; &#x92C;&#x922;&#x93C;&#x93E; &#x926;&#x947;&#x924;&#x947; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902;&#x964; &#x915;&#x94B;&#x930;&#x94B;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x938;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x91A;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x918;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x939;&#x940; &#x915;&#x908; &#x92A;&#x930;&#x924;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x947; &#x938;&#x942;&#x924;&#x940; &#x915;&#x92A;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x938;&#x93F;&#x932;&#x915;&#x930; &#x92A;&#x939;&#x928;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x938;&#x941;&#x930;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x937;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x909;&#x92A;&#x93E;&#x92F; &#x939;&#x948;&#x964; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x92E;&#x939;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x92A;&#x942;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x923; &#x924;&#x925;&#x94D;&#x92F; &#x92B;&#x94D;&#x932;&#x94B;&#x930;&#x93F;&#x921;&#x93E; &#x905;&#x91F;&#x932;&#x93E;&#x902;&#x91F;&#x93F;&#x915; &#x935;&#x93F;&#x936;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x935;&#x93F;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x92F; &#x915;&#x947; &#x935;&#x948;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91E;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915; &#x905;&#x927;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x92F;&#x928; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x938;&#x93E;&#x92E;&#x928;&#x947; &#x906;&#x92F;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x948;&#x964;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#x935;&#x948;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91E;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x928;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x93E;&#x91C;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x906;&#x938;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x940; &#x938;&#x947; &#x909;&#x92A;&#x932;&#x92C;&#x94D;&#x927; &#x915;&#x908; &#x924;&#x930;&#x939; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92B;&#x947;&#x938;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x915;&#x947; &#x938;&#x902;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x923; &#x92B;&#x948;&#x932;&#x928;&#x947; &#x938;&#x947; &#x930;&#x94B;&#x915;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x940; &#x915;&#x94D;&#x937;&#x92E;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x92A;&#x930; &#x905;&#x927;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x92F;&#x928; &#x915;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x964; &#x935;&#x948;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91E;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x928;&#x947; &#x92A;&#x93E;&#x92F;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x915;&#x908; &#x92A;&#x930;&#x924;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x947; &#x938;&#x942;&#x924;&#x940; &#x915;&#x92A;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x92A;&#x939;&#x928;&#x928;&#x947; &#x938;&#x947; &#x921;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x949;&#x92A;&#x932;&#x947;&#x91F; &#x91C;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x926;&#x93E; &#x926;&#x942;&#x930; &#x924;&#x915; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x924;&#x93E;&#x935;&#x930;&#x923; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x92B;&#x948;&#x932; &#x92A;&#x93E;&#x924;&#x940;&#x902;&#x964; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x92A;&#x939;&#x928;&#x947; &#x938;&#x902;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x935;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x941;&#x902;&#x939; &#x938;&#x947; &#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x932;&#x940;&#x902; &#x938;&#x902;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x92C;&#x942;&#x902;&#x926;&#x947;&#x902; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x930; &#x922;&#x93E;&#x908; &#x907;&#x902;&#x91A; &#x924;&#x915; &#x939;&#x940; &#x92B;&#x948;&#x932; &#x938;&#x915;&#x924;&#x940; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902;&#x964; &#x92F;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x940; &#x905;&#x917;&#x930; &#x915;&#x94B;&#x908; &#x90F;&#x915; &#x92E;&#x940;&#x91F;&#x930; &#x915;&#x940; &#x926;&#x942;&#x930;&#x940; &#x92C;&#x928;&#x93E;&#x915;&#x930; &#x916;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x948; &#x924;&#x94B; &#x909;&#x938;&#x947; &#x915;&#x949;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x91F;&#x928; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x915; &#x932;&#x917;&#x93E;&#x90F; &#x935;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x938;&#x947; &#x938;&#x902;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x923; &#x928;&#x939;&#x940;&#x902; &#x939;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x93E;&#x964;</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593963039</statusID><topic>photographed fleeing smoke and debris as the south tower of the World Trade Center crumbled just a block away on Sept. 11, 2001, has died from coronavirus, his family said.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Palm Beach Post reported that Stephen Cooper, an electrical engineer from New York who lived part-time in the Delray Beach, Florida area, died March 28 at Delray Medical Center due to COVID-19. He was 78.&#xD;
&#xD;
The photo, captured by an Associated Press photographer, was published in newspapers and magazines around the world and is featured at the 9/11 Memorial Museum in New York.</topic><post>photographed fleeing smoke and debris as the south tower of the World Trade Center crumbled just a block away on Sept. 11, 2001, has died from coronavirus, his family said.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Palm Beach Post reported that Stephen Cooper, an electrical engineer from New York who lived part-time in the Delray Beach, Florida area, died March 28 at Delray Medical Center due to COVID-19. He was 78.&#xD;
&#xD;
The photo, captured by an Associated Press photographer, was published in newspapers and magazines around the world and is featured at the 9/11 Memorial Museum in New York.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593963082</statusID><topic>Man in famous 9/11 photo dies from COVID-19 in Florida</topic><post>photographed fleeing smoke and debris as the south tower of the World Trade Center crumbled just a block away on Sept. 11, 2001, has died from coronavirus, his family said.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Palm Beach Post reported that Stephen Cooper, an electrical engineer from New York who lived part-time in the Delray Beach, Florida area, died March 28 at Delray Medical Center due to COVID-19. He was 78.&#xD;
&#xD;
The photo, captured by an Associated Press photographer, was published in newspapers and magazines around the</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964043</statusID><topic>photographed fleeing smoke and debris as the south tower of the World Trade </topic><post>Suzanne Plunkett, the Associated Press photographer who snapped the shot, wrote that she&#x2019;s been in touch with two of the people in the photo, but Cooper was not among them.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964091</statusID><topic>Suzanne Plunkett, the Associated Pres but Cooper was not among them.</topic><post>Suzanne Plunkett, the Associated Press photographer who snapped the shot, wrote that she&#x2019;s been in touch with two of the people in the photo, but Cooper was not among them.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964109</statusID><topic>Suzanne Plunkett, the Associated Press photographer who snapped the shot, wrote that she&#x2019;s been in touch with two of the people</topic><post>Suzanne Plunkett, the Associated Press photographer who snapped the shot, wrote that she&#x2019;s been in touch with two of the people in the photo, but Cooper was not among them.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964169</statusID><topic>DGPR of PoK wants freedom from Pakistan; accuses Imran Khan government of human rights violation</topic><post>Awaam of Azad Jammu and Kashmir seek independence from Pakistan. Pakistan Army and police are involved in mass-scale human rights violations, atrocities on innocent civilians and spreading terrorism. We strongly condemn Pakistani rulers for the discriminatory policies and misrule in Azad Jammu and Kashmir for the past 70 years,&#x201D; the message reads.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964222</statusID><topic>Awaam of Azad Jammu and Kashmir seek independence from Pakistan. </topic><post>Pakistan Army and police are involved in mass-scale human rights violations, atrocities on innocent civilians and spreading terrorism. We strongly condemn Pakistani rulers for the discriminatory policies and misrule in Azad Jammu and Kashmir for the past 70 years,&#x201D; the message reads.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964498</statusID><topic>Pakistan Army and police are involved in mass-scale human </topic><post>Pakistan Army and police are involved in mass-scale human rights violations, atrocities on innocent civilians and spreading terrorism. We strongly condemn Pakistani rulers for the discriminatory policies and misrule in Azad Jammu and Kashmir for the past 70 years,&#x201D; the message reads.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964527</statusID><topic>discriminatory policies and misrule in Azad Jammu and Kashmir for the past 70 years,&#x201D; the </topic><post>Pakistan Army and police are involved in mass-scale human rights violations, atro&#xD;
cities on innocent civilians and spreading terrorism. We strongly condemn Pakistani rulers for the message reads.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964681</statusID><topic>A Warning About Call Of Duty: Warzone&#x2019;s Broken Double XP Weekend</topic><post>Players may discover that they are not getting as much XP as they would normally from a double XP weekend, that&#x2019;s because they are getting&#x2026;effectively the non-boosted amount. While double XP is active, the base XP you get has been cut in half. So rather than a 900 XP action getting you 1800 XP, that action now gives 450 XP which doubles to&#x2026;900 XP, exactly the same.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593964737</statusID><topic>PS5 random pricing in Nielsen survey could indicate that Sony has plans to price the PlayStation 5 consoles at an irresistible point</topic><post>Reddit user called u/youessbee has shared some details about a Nielsen survey they took part in. One of the questions was about the PS5 price, which has become one of the most debated topics among PS5 fans. While no actual official prices were offered, the survey suggested random pricing that can be interpreted in a number of ways. The Nielsen statement read as follows:</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593965248</statusID><topic>Assess the impact of global warming on the coral life system with examples.</topic><post>Coral life system harbour the highest biodiversity of any ecosystem globally and directly support over 500 million people worldwide.&#xD;
&#xD;
However, over the last three years, coral reefs ecosystem around the world have suffered from mass coral bleaching events. They are now among the most threatened ecosystems on Earth, largely due to unprecedented global warming and climate changes, combined with growing local pressures.&#xD;
&#xD;
Impact of global warming on the coral life system&#xD;
As temperature rises, mass coral bleaching events and infectious disease outbreaks are becoming more frequent. The bleaching of the Great Barrier Reef in 2016 and 2017, for instance, killed around 50% of its corals.&#xD;
Bleached corals are likely to experience reduced growth rates, decreased reproductive capacity, increased susceptibility to diseases and elevated mortality rates.&#xD;
Ocean acidification, or increased CO2 levels has reduced calcification rates in reef-building and reefassociated organisms, causing their skeletons to become weaker and growth to be impaired.&#xD;
Sea level rise may lead to increases in sedimentation for reefs located near land-based sources of sediment. Sedimentation runoff can lead to the smothering of coral.&#xD;
Changes in storm patterns, due to climate change, may lead to stronger and more frequent storms that can cause the destruction of coral reefs.&#xD;
Changes in coral ecosystem also affect the species that depend on them, such as the fish and invertebrates that rely on live coral for food, shelter, or recruitment habitat.&#xD;
Changes in precipitation result in increased runoff of freshwater, sediment, and land-based pollutants contribute to algal blooms and cause murky water conditions that reduce light.&#xD;
Altered ocean currents lead to changes in connectivity and temperature regimes that contribute to lack of food for corals and hampers dispersal of coral larvae.&#xD;
It is also expected that there will be a gradual decrease in the quantity of marine plants such as phytoplankton in warmer waters, effectively reducing the amount of nutrients available to animals further along the food chain.&#xD;
In addition, the collapse of coral life system due to global warming can have direct impacts on tourism, aquaculture, and pharmaceutical industries as well as reduce the overall resilience of coastal communities.&#xD;
Way forward&#xD;
Limiting global average temperature to well below 2&#xB0;C above pre-industrial levels, addressing local pollution and destructive fishing practices provide chance for the survival of coral life system globally. Also, transformation of mainstream economic systems towards circular economic practices can help in mitigating rising global temperatures.&#xD;
According to UNESCO, the coral reefs in all 29 reef-containing World Heritage sites would cease to exist by the end of this century if global warming is not reduced. Reinforcing commitments to the Paris Agreement may be mirrored in all other global agreements such as the Sustainable Development Goals. SDG 13, for instance, calls for urgent action to combat climate change and its impacts</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593965537</statusID><topic>Discuss the causes of depletion of mangroves and explain their importance in maintaining coastal ecology.</topic><post>NavIC (Navigation with Indian Constellation) is an independent and indigenous regional navigation satellite system developed by India. It is a set of 8 satellites which will be located in suitable orbital slots - geostationary or geosynchronous.&#xD;
&#xD;
It makes India only the sixth country in the world to have its own navigation system.&#xD;
&#xD;
This frees India from dependence on other countries for its navigation (GPS, GLONASS, Galileo etc.).&#xD;
&#xD;
Given that it&#x2019;s primary service area is India and the region extending up to 1500 km from its boundary, it&#x2019;s expected to be more accurate (better than 20 m) and reliable. Also, this will help solidify India&#x2019;s position as a regional power as NavIC will be open for use by India&#x2019;s neighbours as well.&#xD;
&#xD;
Further, it will help meet local user requirements of the positioning, navigation and timing services.&#xD;
&#xD;
Navigation&#xD;
&#xD;
IRNSS will provide two types of navigation services:&#xD;
Standard Positioning Service &#x2013; for all users.&#xD;
Restricted Service &#x2013; an encrypted service only for authourised users.&#xD;
The signals broadcast by IRNSS satellites will transmit navigation service signals (timing and position information) to the users.&#xD;
This data will be used to give users visual and voice navigation assistance.&#xD;
These will form the basis for variety of navigation applications:&#xD;
Land navigation &#x2013; traffic management, tracking train&#x2019;s movement, land survey, etc.&#xD;
Marine navigation &#x2013; fishermen, merchant ships, port operations, disaster management, etc.&#xD;
Aerial navigation &#x2013; civil aviation, military operations, etc.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593965795</statusID><post>How does the Juno Mission of NASA help to understand the origin and evolution of the Earth? (2017)</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593966338</statusID><post>How does the Juno Mission of NASA help to understand the origin and evolution of the Earth? (2017)</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1593966410</statusID><post>How does the Juno Mission of NASA help to understand the origin and evolution of the Earth? (2017)</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594012519</statusID><topic>Q. Explain the significance of the right to protest in a democracy. (250 words)</topic><post>Under Article 19 Indian Constitution guarantees Freedom of Speech and Expression and of Assembly. Right to Protest is implicit under these fundamental rights. Similar rights have been listed out in other democracies too.&#xD;
&#xD;
Body&#xD;
Significance of Right to Protest in a Democracy&#xD;
&#xD;
It helps in empowering individuals and groups to express their point of view, that is not in consonance with the ruling regime and tends to hurt legitimate interest of concerned, for example farmer protesting for land rights, raising income in face of rapid industrialisation.&#xD;
Right to Protest helps set or alter agenda in a debate that transgresses social, political and economic life, for example, following protest over Nirbhaya rape women&#x2019;s security and role in public life came into question resulting in changes at legal and administrative levels like Nirbhaya Fund.&#xD;
Right to Protest is an essential voice for the marginalised section in the democracy, as it allows for their view to be reflected equally and not submerged under majoritarian view.&#xD;
Right to Protest helps bring about change in mindset of citizens, fight discrimination which in turn makes the government more responsive, accountable, responsible to its people, all while making democracy deeper and wider by increasing individual&#x2019;s and social group&#x2019;s stake in the nation-building.&#xD;
But there is no absolute form of such right and have to be qualified in form of reasonable restrictions:&#xD;
&#xD;
Under Article 19, a speech and expression cannot hurt sovereignty, integrity, security, foreign-friendly relations of India, like the case of Naxalism in India.&#xD;
Such rights should not threaten public order, decency/morality, contempt of court, defame or incite offence like communal speech.&#xD;
Conclusion&#xD;
An elected government may stray from the constitutional course, go against the interests of the people, become unresponsive and refuse to listen. Here pressure against the government must be built by still stronger public methods. Right to protest allows the people to become watchdogs in a democracy, and while constantly monitoring the acts of the government it empowers the people to initiate debate on the concerned issues opening up the possibilities of rectification at the government&#x2019;s end.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594055773</statusID><topic>Children\'s are likely to be killed now due to other causes precipitated by covid virus</topic><post>Key drivers for potential death of 12 lakh children could be POVERTY, HUNGER and DISEASE, and lack of proper VACCINATION (For other diseases) and CLINICAL services.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594109654</statusID><post>Finally real kitty is here&#x1F408;&#x1F92D;&#x1F92D;</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594116689</statusID><topic>Dil bechara trailer : Sushant Singh Rajput swansong is a heartbreaking romance</topic><post>Dil Bechara is the official remake of 2014 Hollywood romantic drama The Fault in our Stars based on John Green&#x2019;s popular novel of the same name.&#xD;
&#xD;
Mukesh Chhabra makes his directorial debut with this movie, with the Hindi adaptation by Shashank Khaitan and Suprotim Sengupta. Dil Bechara will see the late Sushant Singh Rajput in a leading role alongside debutante Sanjana Sanghi, and Saif Ali Khan in an interesting cameo. The music for the film is by AR Rahman and lyrics by Amitabh Bhattacharya for the album.&#xD;
&#xD;
The film follows a young couple in love, as they meet and fall for each other. The catch? He&#x2019;s had a brush with osteosarcoma, while she is fighting thyroid cancer.&#xD;
&#xD;
The official synopsis for Dil Bechara states, &#x201C;It is the story of Kizie Basu and Immanuel Rajkumar Junior or Manny and explores the funny, thrilling, and tragic adventure of being alive and in love. Together Kizie and Manny embark on an on-off-up-down-sad and sweet profound journey into the heart of that crazy little thing called life. It teaches them what it means to feel truly alive and fall in love.&#x201D;&#xD;
&#xD;
The film is set for release on July 24 on Disney+ Hotstar.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594116792</statusID><topic>Dil bechara trailer : Sushant Singh Rajput swansong is a heartbreaking romance</topic><post>Dil Bechara is the official remake of 2014 Hollywood romantic drama The Fault in our Stars based on John Green&#x2019;s popular novel of the same name. Mukesh Chhabra makes his directorial debut with this movie, with the Hindi adaptation by Shashank Khaitan and Suprotim Sengupta. Dil Bechara will see the late Sushant Singh Rajput in a leading role alongside debutante Sanjana Sanghi, and Saif Ali Khan in an interesting cameo. The music for the film is by AR Rahman and lyrics by Amitabh Bhattacharya for the album. The film follows a young couple in love, as they meet and fall for each other. The catch? He&#x2019;s had a brush with osteosarcoma, while she is fighting thyroid cancer. The official synopsis for Dil Bechara states, &#x201C;It is the story of Kizie Basu and Immanuel Rajkumar Junior or Manny and explores the funny, thrilling, and tragic adventure of being alive and in love. Together Kizie and Manny embark on an on-off-up-down-sad and sweet profound journey into the heart of that crazy little thing called life. It teaches them what it means to feel truly alive and fall in The film is set for release on July 24 on Disney+ Hotstar.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594116901</statusID><topic>PUBG Mobile 0.19.0 Update: Exclusive Livik map released </topic><post>There will be physical impact of the water flowing from the waterfall. Players might even get washed away by rapid water flow when standing at the top of the waterfall. Along with this, an exclusive vehicle (Monster Truck) has also been added to the game:&#xD;
&#xD;
</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594118856</statusID><topic>&#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x92C;&#x915; &#x938;&#x940;&#x916;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x92D;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x924;&#x940;&#x92F; &#x909;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x92A;&#x924;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x938;&#x940; &#x915;&#x92E;&#x930;, &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; &#x917;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x941;&#x92A; &#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x93E; &#x92C;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x93E; &#x910;&#x932;&#x93E;&#x928;</topic><post>&#x928;&#x908; &#x926;&#x93F;&#x932;&#x94D;&#x932;&#x940;&#x903; &#x91C;&#x947;&#x90F;&#x938;&#x921;&#x92C;&#x94D;&#x932;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x942; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x942;&#x939; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x932;&#x93F;&#x915; &#x938;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91C;&#x928; &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; &#x928;&#x947; &#x938;&#x94B;&#x92E;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x938;&#x947; &#x906;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x924; &#x92C;&#x902;&#x926; &#x915;&#x930;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x909;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x92A;&#x924;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x940;&#x91A; &#x90F;&#x915;&#x91C;&#x941;&#x91F;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93E; &#x906;&#x939;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x928; &#x915;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x964; &#x909;&#x928;&#x94D;&#x939;&#x94B;&#x902;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x910;&#x938;&#x947; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x92F; &#x91C;&#x92C; &#x935;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x935;&#x93F;&#x915; &#x928;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x902;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x923; &#x930;&#x947;&#x916;&#x93E; (&#x90F;&#x932;&#x90F;&#x938;&#x940;) &#x92A;&#x930; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928;&#x940; &#x939;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x947; &#x938;&#x948;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x930;&#x939;&#x947; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902; &#x926;&#x94B;&#x928;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x926;&#x947;&#x936;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x940;&#x91A; &#x935;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x92A;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x92A;&#x939;&#x932;&#x947; &#x915;&#x940; &#x924;&#x930;&#x939; &#x91C;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x940; &#x928;&#x939;&#x940;&#x902; &#x930;&#x939; &#x938;&#x915;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x948;&#x964; &#xD;
&#xD;
&#x907;&#x938;&#x938;&#x947; &#x92A;&#x939;&#x932;&#x947; &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x947;&#x91F;&#x947; &#x92A;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x925; &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; &#x928;&#x947; &#x92D;&#x940; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E; &#x925;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x909;&#x928;&#x915;&#x93E; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x942;&#x939; &#x905;&#x917;&#x932;&#x947; &#x926;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x93E;&#x932; &#x915;&#x947; &#x926;&#x94C;&#x930;&#x93E;&#x928; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x938;&#x947; 40 &#x915;&#x930;&#x94B;&#x921;&#x93C; &#x921;&#x949;&#x932;&#x930; &#x915;&#x93E; &#x906;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x924; &#x92C;&#x902;&#x926; &#x915;&#x930;&#x947;&#x917;&#x93E;&#x964; &#x92A;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x925; &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; 14 &#x905;&#x930;&#x92C; &#x921;&#x949;&#x932;&#x930; &#x915;&#x947; &#x91C;&#x947;&#x90F;&#x938;&#x921;&#x92C;&#x94D;&#x932;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x942; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x942;&#x939; &#x915;&#x947; &#x938;&#x940;&#x92E;&#x947;&#x902;&#x91F; &#x915;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94B;&#x92C;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x926;&#x947;&#x916;&#x924;&#x947; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902;&#x964; &#x917;&#x932;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x928; &#x918;&#x93E;&#x91F;&#x940; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x939;&#x93E;&#x932; &#x939;&#x940; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x92D;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x924;&#x940;&#x92F; &#x914;&#x930; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928;&#x940; &#x938;&#x948;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x940;&#x91A; &#x939;&#x941;&#x90F; &#x938;&#x902;&#x918;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x937; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x947; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x909;&#x928;&#x94D;&#x939;&#x94B;&#x902;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x926;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x93E; &#x92D;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x924;&#x940;&#x92F; &#x92D;&#x942;&#x92E;&#x93F; &#x92A;&#x930; &#x91C;&#x94B; &#x915;&#x941;&#x91B; &#x915;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x93E; &#x917;&#x92F;&#x93E; &#x909;&#x938;&#x915;&#x940; &#x935;&#x91C;&#x939; &#x938;&#x947; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x915;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x908; &#x939;&#x941;&#x908;&#x964; &#xD;
&#xD;
&#x938;&#x91C;&#x94D;&#x91C;&#x928; &#x91C;&#x93F;&#x902;&#x926;&#x932; &#x928;&#x947; &#x90F;&#x915; &#x935;&#x915;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x935;&#x94D;&#x92F; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E;, &#x2018;&#x2018;&#x939;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x947; &#x938;&#x948;&#x928;&#x93F;&#x915; &#x90F;&#x932;&#x90F;&#x938;&#x940; &#x92A;&#x930; &#x909;&#x928;&#x915;&#x947; &#x926;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x93E; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x947; &#x91C;&#x93E;&#x924;&#x947; &#x930;&#x939;&#x947;&#x902; &#x914;&#x930; &#x939;&#x92E; &#x905;&#x92A;&#x928;&#x947; &#x909;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x938;&#x947; &#x938;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x91A;&#x94D;&#x91A;&#x93E; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x932; &#x916;&#x930;&#x940;&#x926;&#x915;&#x930; &#x915;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x908; &#x915;&#x930;&#x924;&#x947; &#x930;&#x939;&#x947;&#x902; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x928;&#x939;&#x940;&#x902; &#x939;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x915;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x948;&#x964;'' &#x909;&#x928;&#x94D;&#x939;&#x94B;&#x902;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x909;&#x928;&#x915;&#x947; &#x915;&#x908; &#x926;&#x94B;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924; &#x914;&#x930; &#x938;&#x939;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x940; &#x909;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x92A;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x907;&#x938; &#x92C;&#x93E;&#x924; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x932;&#x947;&#x915;&#x930; &#x92A;&#x930;&#x947;&#x936;&#x93E;&#x928; &#x939;&#x948; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x92C;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x93E; &#x92E;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x91C;&#x93F;&#x928; &#x915;&#x92E;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x947; &#x914;&#x930; &#x915;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94B;&#x92C;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x928;&#x93F;&#x930;&#x902;&#x924;&#x930;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x92C;&#x928;&#x93E;&#x90F; &#x930;&#x916;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x915;&#x947; &#x938;&#x93E;&#x925; &#x909;&#x928;&#x915;&#x93E; &#x935;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x92A;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x939;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x92A;&#x942;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x923; &#x939;&#x948; &#x932;&#x947;&#x915;&#x93F;&#x928; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x938;&#x94D;&#x925;&#x93F;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x924;&#x92C; &#x906;&#x908; &#x939;&#x948; &#x91C;&#x92C; &#x939;&#x92E;&#x928;&#x947; &#x905;&#x92A;&#x928;&#x947; &#x918;&#x930;&#x947;&#x932;&#x942; &#x906;&#x92A;&#x942;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93E;&#x913;&#x902; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x935;&#x93F;&#x915;&#x938;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x915;&#x930;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92C;&#x91C;&#x93E;&#x92F; &#x906;&#x902;&#x916; &#x92E;&#x942;&#x902;&#x926;&#x915;&#x930; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x915;&#x947; &#x938;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x947; &#x906;&#x92F;&#x93E;&#x924; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x940;&#x915;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x915;&#x930;&#x924;&#x947; &#x930;&#x939;&#x947;&#x964;&#xD;
&#xD;
&#x926;&#x947;&#x936; &#x915;&#x947; &#x907;&#x938; &#x92A;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x92E;&#x941;&#x916; &#x909;&#x926;&#x94D;&#x92F;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x92A;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x939;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x939;&#x92E; &#x938;&#x92D;&#x940; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x947; &#x90F;&#x915; &#x92E;&#x94C;&#x915;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x948; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x939;&#x92E; &#x90F;&#x915;&#x938;&#x93E;&#x925; &#x906;&#x92F;&#x947;&#x902; &#x914;&#x930; &#x92E;&#x91C;&#x92C;&#x942;&#x924; &#x906;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x92E; &#x928;&#x93F;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x92D;&#x930; &#x92D;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x924; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x92F;&#x947; &#x915;&#x93E;&#x92E; &#x915;&#x930;&#x947;&#x902;&#x917;&#x947;&#x964; &#x2018;&#x2018;&#x917;&#x941;&#x923;&#x935;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x93E; &#x914;&#x930; &#x906;&#x915;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x939;&#x93E;&#x938;&#x93F;&#x932; &#x915;&#x930;&#x928;&#x947; &#x915;&#x947; &#x932;&#x93F;&#x90F; &#x906;&#x913; &#x939;&#x92E; &#x918;&#x930;&#x947;&#x932;&#x942; &#x909;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x92A;&#x93E;&#x926;&#x915;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x93E; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x93F;&#x93E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x928; &#x915;&#x930;&#x947;&#x902;&#x964; &#x939;&#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x905;&#x92A;&#x928;&#x947; &#x916;&#x941;&#x926; &#x915;&#x947; &#x909;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x92A;&#x93E;&#x926;&#x94B;&#x902; &#x915;&#x947; &#x92A;&#x94D;&#x930;&#x924;&#x93F; &#x935;&#x93F;&#x936;&#x94D;&#x935;&#x93E;&#x938; &#x926;&#x93F;&#x916;&#x93E;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x93E;&#x964; &#x939;&#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x905;&#x92A;&#x928;&#x940; &#x938;&#x936;&#x938;&#x94D;&#x924;&#x94D;&#x930; &#x938;&#x947;&#x928;&#x93E;&#x913;&#x902; &#x914;&#x930; &#x938;&#x930;&#x915;&#x93E;&#x930; &#x915;&#x94B; &#x938;&#x92E;&#x930;&#x94D;&#x925;&#x928; &#x926;&#x947;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x93E; &#x914;&#x930; &#x92F;&#x939; &#x938;&#x93E;&#x92C;&#x93F;&#x924; &#x915;&#x930;&#x928;&#x93E; &#x939;&#x94B;&#x917;&#x93E; &#x915;&#x93F; &#x91A;&#x940;&#x928; &#x915;&#x947; &#x916;&#x93F;&#x932;&#x93E;&#x92B; &#x932;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x93E;&#x908; &#x92E;&#x947;&#x902; &#x939;&#x92E; &#x909;&#x928;&#x915;&#x947; &#x938;&#x93E;&#x925; &#x916;&#x921;&#x93C;&#x947; &#x939;&#x948;&#x902;&#x964;''</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594145297</statusID><topic>Where will black money hide now? Modi has shrunk illicit money&#x2019;s pit; real estate transparency jumps</topic><post>Prime Minister Narendra Modi government&#x2019;s reforms have shrunk one of the biggest pits of black money in India &#x2014; the country&#x2019;s real estate sector has become more transparent, climbing up five places in a global ranking in the last six years. With the amendment in the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA), transparency in India&#x2019;s real estate sector has significantly improved. In the last two years, transparency in the real estate sector has improved at the second-highest pace in the world, after UAE. With the enhanced transparency and trust in real estate investments, enhanced market data, and sustainability initiatives, India has jumped to the 34th position in the JLL and La Salle&#x2019;s &#x2018;Global Real Estate Transparency Index, 2020&#x2019;. India&#x2019;s rank has improved from 39 to 34 in the last six years.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594184031</statusID><topic>Modern Warfare dev shares exploratory concept art for canceled Zombies mode</topic><post>An Infinity Ward artist has posted on his Instagram account, after getting clearance from Activision and Infinity Ward, exploratory concept art for a Zombies mode idea for Call of Duty: Modern Warfare.Infinity Ward opted out of releasing a Zombies mode with Modern Warfare to preserve the game&#x2019;s authenticity. The game featured Campaign, MP, and Special Ops as a unified game versus having Zombies.</post><postpic>106085877_728589191209412_3304296731956137986_n.jpg</postpic><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594303528</statusID><post>Heyy</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594303561</statusID><post>Heyyyy</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594303567</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304255</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304307</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304451</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304467</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304481</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304700</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304710</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304807</statusID><post>Wow</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594304994</statusID><post>Wowwww</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594352188</statusID><topic>Assassin\'s Creed Valhalla leak features a magical boss fight</topic><post>The map makes a brief appearance, too, giving us a look at Mercia and East Anglia, of which only a tiny portion has been explored. The regions have a suggested power level, and there are progress meters for wealth, mysteries and secrets, which will presumably fill up as you uncover treasure and other hidden items. </post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594501800</statusID><topic>Sathankulam custodial deaths: RJ Suchitra deletes viral video, claims police threatened her with arrest</topic><post>In her video, Suchitra had narrated in vivid detail of how Sathankulam police officials tortured Jeyaraj (62) and Bennicks (32) inside the station. Soon after the video went viral, the issue was debated widely in national television channels.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594583465</statusID><topic>WhatsApp and Facebook Messenger could be merging</topic><post>Facebook Messenger and WhatsApp could be merging which would allow users to chat across apps, no matter which one they themselves are using.&#xD;
&#xD;
Facebook - which has owned WhatsApp since 2014 - is said to be testing the new feature, according to WABetaInfo, which regularly trawls the code of apps to uncover clues to upcoming features with some degree of accuracy.&#xD;
&#xD;
The website said it found evidence of the merge within the code of Facebook Messenger, though it's unclear when the feature could be rolled out.</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594879365</statusID><post>Bsbssbsb</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1594879372</statusID><post>Manish</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1595000372</statusID><topic>Aha</topic><post>Bshs</post><postpic>Screenshot_20200717-205713~2.png</postpic><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1595276255</statusID><topic/><post>H</post><postpic>Brittany_Before_02.jpg</postpic><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1595316299</statusID><topic/><post>dd</post><postpic>IMG_20180110_140248-04.jpeg</postpic><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1595325337</statusID><topic/><post>klflfiae wuhfiureghrgheu</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1595699971</statusID><topic/><post>fasdffasdfdfsa</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1596043555</statusID><topic/><post>rgsvdsgsdfgfgg</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1596651751</statusID><topic/><post>Hhhhhhhhhhhhhjdjjdjdjdjdjdjdjjddjdjdjdjdjdjdnnddnjsjsdjdndndjdjdjdjdndjdjjjddjdjdjsndnsjjsdjdjjxjxdjjxxjxjxjjxjxjddjjdjdjdjddjjddjxj</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>manish</username><statusID>1598553062</statusID><post>Xbdndndjdn djddjdndnd sjsns djdjd sn</post><tag>motive</tag></postset></posts>
