<?xml version="1.0"?>
<posts category="short"><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595221179</statusID><post>Picture perfect u don't need no filter</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595221181</statusID><post>Picture perfect u don't need no filter</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595249539</statusID><post>Samsung Galaxy M31s will launch in India on July 30 at 12pm (noon), an official poster on the Amazon India website revealed. As the name suggests, the upcoming Samsung phone will be a new addition to the Galaxy M31 family, that was first launched in India in February this year. According to the Galaxy M31s micro-site on Amazon, the phone will pack a quad rear camera setup that includes a 64-megapixel primary camera. The camera supports Samsung's Single Take feature that allows users to capture multiple photos and videos with just one take.</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595589942</statusID><topic/><post>Jdjdjd&#xD;
Dkdkdm&#xD;
Djdjd&#xD;
Djjdjd&#xD;
Djjxxndnd&#xD;
Djjddjdjdjdjdjdjdjdjdj</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595590462</statusID><topic/><post>Jdjdjddnd sdjdjdjsjxjs</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595699012</statusID><topic/><post>Hsbdjdxjdj</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595699033</statusID><topic/><post>Hf vhy</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595699274</statusID><topic/><post>Fjchfyfcfctc</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595702778</statusID><topic/><post>A software engineer was arrested for allegedly hacking into the database of his former company and deleting selective information in order to get back his job which he lost during the lockdown, police said on Friday.&#xD;
</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595736243</statusID><topic/><post>Jddjd dnddnd d bdddd dndjd dbxhbe djdbd dbdjd sbdjd ed jdebd bdjd</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595879625</statusID><post>Firstly, to restore normalcy, there must be a democratic space for the people. This requires a freely elected legislature,</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1595953049</statusID><post>In latest development to the Sushant Rajput's death probe, on Tuesday, the actor's father has f</post><tag>motive</tag></postset><postset><username>vergo</username><statusID>1596114845</statusID><topic/><post>to begin. But back home in India, the Kapoors have already started celebrating the 37-year-old entrepreneur's birthday on social media. The first of the Kapoors to wish Anand was Sonam's fath</post><postpic/><tag>#post</tag></postset></posts>
